Vinay Joshi

Email: vinay01joshi@gmail.com

Phone: +91 82856 11645



Summary

expertise & experience in Azure C#, Asp.net,Asp.Net MVC, SQL Server, SQLCE, Mysql, Windows Mobile 6.0 Application. in Client Server technology and file server technology with an exposure to different platforms and software systems. Possess A qualified IT Professional rich experience in Analyzing, Designing, Development, and Implementation of business applications

So what makes me unique? # I write clean, dry, solid code that anyone can read using best practices. People I worked with application two days before it was due. This helped our relation team close a bigger deal with the client, which I am now working we were at least one month behind. I was able to bring our team together, and we were able to finish the fully tested final know me as a hard worker. For example, a project I worked on was nearing the deadline, but for reasons outside of our control,

Experience

| D | |
|----|--|
| 유 | |
| Ĭ | |
| Ş | |
| -7 | |
| | |

Senior Software Engineering

Optum (formerly Alere Wellbeing)



Senior Associate Technology

SapientRazorfish



Associate Technology L2

Feb 2014 - Dec 2016

Jan 2017 - Jul 2018

Jul 2018 - Present

Oct 2011 - Feb 2014

SapientNitro



Senior Software Developer

NextGen Invent Corporation



Software Developer

Oct 2011 - Feb 2014

Jul 2011 - Sep 2011

NextGen Invent Corporation



Corporate Trainer

HPES

Working as a Dot Net Technical Support (Trainer)

Education



2008-2011 Dehradun Institute of Technology (U.T.U. Dehardun)

Master of Computer Applications (MCA), computers, 73



P.G.Collage Rishikesh

BSC, Math, Physics, Geology

2005 - 2007

2008 - 2011